Our preferred pdf setting in InDesign is the PDF/X-1a:2001 that can be created following these steps:

1.     Choose File > Adobe PDF Presets > PDF/X-1a:2001
2.     Click Marks And Bleed on the left side of the Print dialog box.
3.     Select Crop Marks only, do not check any other boxes. Print-Tech only needs crop marks.
4.     To override bleed settings in the Document Setup dialog box, uncheck Use Document
        Bleed Settings and enter 0.2" for Top, Bottom, Left, and
        Right (for single-sided documents), or Top, Bottom, Inside, and Outside
        (for double‑sided documents with facing pages). To extend the offset evenly on
        all sides of the page, click the Make All Settings The Same icon (the chain link icon).
5.     Click Include Slug Area to print objects using the slug area defined in the
        Document Setup dialog box.